THIS. THEY'RE SO GLAD
THAT WE CAN MAKE
OUR WISH COME TRUE.
AND OVER IN LONDON,
WE'RE SURPRISING MAISIE, WHO
IS A MASSIVE FEEDER
FAN WITH A VIP
EXPERIENCE. WELL, DON'T GET
SCARED. BUT OUR NEXT
MISSION WAS WITH BLUE
ORIGIN AND SPACEX,
WHERE THE KIDS GOT
TO SIGN AN ACTUAL
FALCON 9 ROCKET AHEAD
OF ITS LAUNCH.
WHILE HARRY AND BRIAN
GOT TO LIVE OUT
THEIR F1 DREAM.
AND IN PARIS... TAKE
OFF YOUR BLINDFOLD.
I HEARD YOU GUYS
WERE BIG FANS OF
THE CHANNEL.
FOUR KIDS COMPETED IN
A MISCHIEVOUS CHALLENGE.
PAIN AT THE MR.
BEAST LOGO.
AND NOW IT'S HANGING
ON MY WALLS.
JIMMY, WHAT ABOUT MINE?
NOLAN, WHAT IS THAT?
I HEARD YOU GUYS
WERE BIG FANS OF
THE CHANNEL.
HOW'S GOING?
OH, THANK YOU. THESE
KIDS JUST WANTED TO
MEET ME. BUT I
BROUGHT IN SOMEONE EVEN
TALLER. I HEARD THAT
YOU GUYS WERE FANS
OF BASKETBALL.
YOU'RE NOT JUST MEETING
ME TODAY. YOU'RE ALSO
GOING TO BE MEETING
THE GREATEST BASKETBALL PLAYER
TO EVER LIVE THE
FRANCHISE.
ALL RIGHT, THANKS FOR
MAKING IT UP. THAT
WAS AWESOME.
MAYBE IF YOU'RE LUCKY,
YOU CAN CONVINCE THEM
TO SHOOT A SHOT
REAL QUICK. YEAH, I
CAN DO THAT. I'M
NOT IN A DREAM.
I THOUGHT I IN
A DREAM. YOU HIT
RIGHT ON THAT SQUARE.
OH, THERE WE GO.
THERE GO.
I GOT SOMETHING SPECIAL
FOR YOU GUYS. I
AM HANDING OVER THE
KEYS TO MY FOUNDATION'S
HOUSE 330 THAT'S DOWN
THE STREET FOR UNBELIEVABLE
EXPERIENCE FOR YOU GUYS.
THIS IS ALL I
HAVE. NOT ONLY DOES
THIS FOUNDATION DOUBLE AS
A COMMUNITY CENTER WITH
GAMES AND FOOD.
I KIND OF WANT
SOME OF THAT CARAMEL
-FUDGE BROWNIE. BROWNS FOUNDATION
IS COMMITTED TO REDEFINING
COMMUNITY AND BUILDING STRONGER
FAMILIES THAN AKRON. AND
IT EVEN HAS HIS
BEDROOM. DON'T MIND ME.
UH, LEBRON, DON'T WORRY.
WE'RE TAKING GOOD CARE
OF THE PLACE. REAL
GOOD, LEBRON. LOOK WHO
CALLED ME.
I'M NOT STOPPING THERE.
I BROUGHT THE NEXT
KIDS TO ONE OF
THE BIGGEST MOLES IN
THE WORLD. EVERYBODY TAKE
OFF YOUR BLINDFOLDS.
THIS IS YOURS FOR
THE ENTIRE DAY. YOU
CAN DO WHATEVER YOU
WANT. YOU WANT TO
GO TO THE THEME
PARK? YEAH! ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GO AHEAD IT.
MANY OF THESE KIDS
HAVE BARELY BEEN ABLE
TO EXPERIENCE ANYTHING BECAUSE
OF THEIR CANCER TREATMENTS.
SO I DECIDED TO
RENT OUT AND SURPRISE
THEM WITH A PLACE
THAT HAS LITERALLY EVERYTHING.
WHAT'S